{
    "id": "d70e8798c0f44ed89aa1a1798c9628ee",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She wouldn’t have lost her job, ………………………… she had met her targets.",
            "description": "If is used to express a condition. ",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a331e9d5d91c4fdc80e5a44354c6f5d5"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. she arrives now, we will have to go without her.",
            "description": "Unless also expresses a condition. It means if not.",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dc2511f4d02b40e2b724e14cc4a3ad8b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t know …………………………… I will have time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c6397fa6648b40e4ba2aaace35be64f4"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… she invited me, I would not go to her party.",
            "description": "Even if refers to the present or future. ",
            "answers": [
                "Even if",
                "If",
                "Even though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "413bb652b2f74334b23a3958e7db7b27"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will do it …………………………….. you like it or not.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whether",
                "that",
                "if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "507fe7c70f0a4da8991a595389a646ff"
        },
        {
            "question": "I admired him ……………………………… people said that he was a traitor.",
            "description": "Although is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "as",
                "even if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "07be23b32d51444eaa2b25b95128c7c4"
        },
        {
            "question": "She missed school ……………………………… she was ill.",
            "description": "Because gives the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "so",
                "hence"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2003bf0ba4ea4d9e8df291fb7b3573fb"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was sacked ……………………………… the manager was not happy with her performance.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "so",
                "thus"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3b5a80e551974f71b0bcba420f97a929"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… she gets good treatment, she will not survive.",
            "description": "Unless means if not.",
            "answers": [
                "Unless",
                "If",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9fe61438cd2b4884abae4c991670a878"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. it was a holiday, I spent the whole day in bed.",
            "description": "As can introduce the reason for something. ",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "So",
                "While"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "691816886b0243feb3f75d0f6a3367e9"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was so beautiful ……………………………. everybody admired her.",
            "description": "Note the pattern so..that...",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "and",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5f0bf05e145945b4a72164d159fdd0d7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I went home ………………………………. I was bored.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "so",
                "hence"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bc38c98b01a74e8a992b50290fc6c5fe"
        }
    ]
}